<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dont Text</title>
    <link>https://donttext.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dont Text</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:57:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://donttext.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Block Spam Texts on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/blog/how-to-block-spam-texts-on-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:57:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/blog/how-to-block-spam-texts-on-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Unsolicited text messages can be really annoying. If your iPhone is being bombarded with spam text messages you need some way to get rid of them.
iPhones do not offer a built in solution for blocking spam texts. In order to block them, you will need to use a third-party app.
Install Dont Text Dont Text makes it simple to block spam texts messages on your iPhone. To get started, download Dont Text from the App Store for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End User License Agreement</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 01:27:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/tos/</guid>
      <description>Dont Text is licensed to You (End-User) by Tyler Kennedy for use only under the terms of this License Agreement.
By downloading the Application from the Apple AppStore, and any update thereto (as permitted by this License Agreement), You indicate that You agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions of this License Agreement, and that You accept this License Agreement.
The parties of this License Agreement acknowledge that Apple is not a Party to this License Agreement and is not bound by any provisions or obligations with regard to the Application, such as warranty, liability, maintenance and support thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 01:27:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/privacy/</guid>
      <description>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Interpretation and Definitions Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 22:28:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/faq/</guid>
      <description>General Do you have an android app? Dont Text is only available for iOS devices.
How do I enable text message filtering?  Download our app from the App Store Go to settings Scroll down and tap on Messages Scroll down and tap on Spam &amp;amp; Filtering Select Dont Text to allow our app to filter your messages  Why isn&amp;rsquo;t the app working, it&amp;rsquo;s not blocking spam texts? Make sure you followed the steps above to enable text filtering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 22:28:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/download/</guid>
      <description>   Download Dont Text From the App Store   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
