<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Dont Text</title>
    <link>https://donttext.app/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Dont Text</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 22:42:11 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://donttext.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Am I Getting Spam Text Messages?</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/blog/why-am-i-getting-spam-text-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 17:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/blog/why-am-i-getting-spam-text-messages/</guid>
      <description>Are you suddenly getting a ton of spam text messages? Have you ever wondered how spammers get your phone number in the first place? Here&amp;rsquo;s some truth, your phone number is not as secret as it seems.
You probably don&amp;rsquo;t have a phone book at home anymore, but now it&amp;rsquo;s easier than ever to lookup someone&amp;rsquo;s phone number online. There are massive databases of phone numbers available on the internet. With a name and a location, you might even be able to find someone&amp;rsquo;s number with that information alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Block Spam Texts on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://donttext.app/blog/how-to-block-spam-texts-on-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:57:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://donttext.app/blog/how-to-block-spam-texts-on-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Unsolicited text messages are really annoying. If your iPhone is being bombarded with spam text messages you need a way to block them.
iPhones offer a few options for stopping spam texts. Apple provides documentation on blocking spam text messages with iOS.
If you want to save a little time reading, here is a quick summary of the steps you can take to remove unwanted texts from your iPhone:
Block the Spam Text Sender The easiest way to stop spam texts is to block the sender.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
